

SOWJANYA C V

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am an front-end developer with an experience of over 1 year. I have worked on building websites that seamlessly transform from one platform to another. I am interested in applying technical skills and looking forward to work in a competitive environment that can boost my overall learning.



+81 9020997417



priya99vish@gmail.com



https://sowjanyaportfolio.g atsbyjs.io/



www.linkedin.com/in/sowjanya-c-v

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Notespace Inc • Feb 2022 to Dec 2022

- Produced TypeScript and Reactjs code to create efficient and clean websites.
- Improved coding of JavaScript and CSS to enhance user experience and functionality.

System Engineer

Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO), LRDE • Sep 2021 to Jan 2022

- Worked as a system engineer in this government laboratory.
- Specialized in HTML, JavaScript and CSS

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

New Horizon College of Engineering

Information Science, Class of 2021

- 8.62 CGPA average of 7 semesters
- Campus Ambassador, Lowes India
- Vice President, VMware IT Academy Club

Kendriya Vidyalaya, DRDO

Higher Secondary - Class of 2017

- 65.5% PCMC Group
- Co Curricular Activity Captain for Prithvi House in Grade 12

Secondary school- Class of 2015

- 10 CGPA in 10th Grade
- Recipient of Dr. R P Shenoy Award for Excellence in Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- HTML, CSS
- Reactis
- Vuejs
- Chakra UI

LANGUAGES KNOWN

English, Hindi, Telugu, Kannada, Japanese

PROJECTS

- Meme Generator React + TS + ChakraUI
- FoodPrint React + JS + ChakraUI

INTERESTS

- Painting
- Blogging
- Reading
- Playing Guitar